2createawebsites.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy - How To Create A Website

PUBLISHED: FEBRUARY 21, 2014 – ARTICLE: PRIVACY POLICY

Privacy Policy for [How To Create a Website](http://www.2createawebsites.com/ "Visit our home page to find out more."). We recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

Below is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit www.2createawebsites.com, and how we safeguard your information. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our all our page’s where personally identifiable information may be requested.

We never sell any kind of personal information that has been collected to third parties or use this data for any illegal activities.

## Cookies

Cookies are used to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit this site. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York restaurants to New York residents, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing web design ads to someone who frequents web design sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

## Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of [DoubleClick DART Cookie](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/) by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, www.2createawebsites.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Email Addresses

If you contact us from our email address we will never sell or give your email address away.

Please Share

Create An Online Shop

Build your own website and sell stuff. Add as many products as you want and it won't cost you any extra. 

Get super fast hosting  
Free domain registration  
Outstanding reliability  
Free shopping basket  
Easy to use site builder

Try creating your website free for 30 days. No credit card required, click the below link.

Build and host your own website on super fast reliable hosting.

Free domain included or add a domain you own - Install WordPress in a few clicks - Great support team.

Get a Website that Works. It's quick and easy. No experience necessary.

Sign up today and get 20 percent off your hosting.
